瑞秋 我们这边只剩几张履历表了
Rach, we're running low on résumés over here.
你真的想去《大众机械杂志》做事？
Do you really want a job with Popular Mechanics?
要是想为机械工做点事 那倒是不错的选择
Well, if you're gonna work for mechanics, those are the ones to work for.
说真的 我现在什么都可以做了 好吗？
Hey, look, you guys. I'm going for anything here, okay?
我不想再当服务生了 真的
I can't be a waitress anymore. I mean it.
小费那么少 烦死了 而且大家都叫我"不好意思"
I'm sick of the lousy tips. I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
瑞秋 你写完后 有没有检查？
Rach, did you proofread these?
有啊 怎么了？
Uh, yeah. Why?
没什么 你优秀的电"恼"能力 我相信大家都会印象深刻
Uh, nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed with your excellent "compuper" skills.
我的天
Oh, my God!
每一张上面都写这样吗？
Oh, do you think it's on all of them?
不会啦 我相信影印机一定帮你抓到几个错误了
Oh, no, I'm sure the Xerox machine caught a few.
- 大家好   - 嘿
- Hey, guys.     - Hey.
嘿 两位小姐
Hey. Hi, ladies.
要点什么饮料？
Uh, can I get you anything?
- 去拿信了吗？ - 一堆回信
- Did you bring the mail?     - Lots of responses.
真的吗？当然还有司康松糕罗
Really? Sure we have scones left.
好 念给我听
Okay, read them to me.
"亲爱的葛林小姐: 谢谢您的申请 不过…"
"Dear Miss Green: Thank you for your inquiry. However..."
- 我们有苹果肉挂…   - 好 "亲爱的葛林小姐"…
- We have apple cinnamon...     - Okay, "Dear Miss Green"...
好 好 好 不行
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. No.
- 哇   - 什么啊？
- Wow.     - What?
你的卡债还真多
Your Visa bill is huge.
拿来
Give me that.
我真不敢相信 琳达这么可爱
You know, I can't believe you. Linda is so great.
- 你为什么不约她出去？ - 不知道
- Why won't you go out with her again?     - I don't know.
你是不是还在想…
Is this still about her whole...
她说的"《摩登原始人》有可能是真的"？
..."The Flintstones could have really happened" thing?
不只是那样
It's not just that.
我只是想要一个能让我心动…
It's just, I want someone who does something for me...
让我小鹿乱撞…
...you know, who gets my heart pounding...
让我…
...who makes me, uh...
身上穿毛衣的小东西？
Little play things with yarn?
什么啊？
What?
还有人更让你心动的吗？
Could you want her more?
谁？
Who?
还有谁？就是肥皂剧里那个女生啊
Who? Dee, the sarcastic sister from What's Happening!!
谁啊？
Who?
说真的 我对她完全没有感觉了 好吗？
Look, I am totally, totally over her, okay?
- 我只是… 嘿   - 嘿 还要咖啡吗？
- I just... Hi.     - Hi. Coffee?
- 不了 这样就好   - 好
- No, we're fine.     - Okay.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我们什么都没说哦
We're not saying anything.
- 什么啊？ - 乔伊昨晚哭了
- What?     - Uh, Joey cried last night.
谢谢哦
Thank you.
我们不是在玩牌吗？
We were playing poker, right?
3号牌上有巧克力 所以看起来像8好吗？
There was chocolate on the three. It looked like an eight, all right?
应该让你们看看 《看着看着就哭了》
Oh, God, you should've seen him. "Read them and weep."
他也照办了
And then he did.
你们怎么从来不跟我们玩牌？
Well, now, how come you guys have never played poker with us?
对啊 怎么回事？就是只有男生能玩吗？
Yeah, what is that? Like some kind of guy thing?
就是只有性别歧视的男生能玩吗？
Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
扑克牌只有男生能玩啊？
Like, it's poker, so only guys can play?
我们也很欢迎女生玩
No. Women are welcome to play.
哦 那怎么了？
Oh, okay, so then what is it?
就是… 就是…
Some kind of, you know, like, some kind of, you know, like...
好吧 到底是怎样？
All right, what is it?
就只是刚好我们玩牌时 没有女人
There just don't happen to be any women in our game.
对啊 我们不认识会玩扑克牌的女人
Yeah, we just don't happen to know any women that know how to play poker.
拜托 烂借口 标准的男生答案
Oh, please. That is such a lame excuse. I mean, it's a typical guy response.
不好意思 你们当中有人会玩吗？
Excuse me, do any of you know how to play?
不会
No.
但是你们可以教我们
But you could teach us.
不要
No.
好 现在我们抽牌
Okay, so now we draw cards.
我这样不需要再抽了吧？我有顺子
So I wouldn't need any, right? Because I have a straight.
- 太好了   - 恭喜你
- Oh, good for you.     - Congratulations.
好 菲比 你要几张？
Okay, Pheebs, how many do you want?
我要两张 黑桃10跟梅花6
Okay, I just need two. The 10 of spades and the six of clubs.
不行 菲比 不可以这样
No, uh, Pheebs, you can't do that.
我有黑桃10 你要不要？
I have the 10 of spades. Here, you want it?
谢谢
Thanks.
不行 不可以这样子
Uh, no, see, uh, you can't do that.
没关系 我不需要这张牌 我要四张四
No, no. That's okay. I don't need them. I'm going for fours.
啊 你在…
Oh, you're...
好 上菜了
All right, here we go.
这是鲑鱼轮盘跟什锦生菜棒
We've got salmon roulettes and assorted crudités.
摩妮卡 你在干什么？
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Monica, what are you doing?
我们在玩扑克牌 只能吃垃圾零食
This is a poker game. You can't serve food with more than one syllable.
像洋芋片 蝴蝶脆饼…
It's got to be like chips or dip or pretz...
好 现在庄家…
Okay, so at this point, the dealer...
这样好了 开始玩真的吧 我们会了 高风险 玩真钱
You know what? We got it. We got it. Let's play for real. High stakes. Big bucks.
你确定吗？菲比刚丢出两张J…
All right, now, you sure? Phoebe just threw away two jacks...
因为它们看起来很不快乐
...because they didn't look happy.
但是我可以玩了 发牌吧
But I'm ready. So just deal.
好 最后一课 最后一课 乔伊
Okay, all right, last minute lesson. Last minute lesson. Joey.
Three...
...eight.
8 3 好 可以开始了
Eight, three. All right. Here we go.
该死 该死 该死
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
我知道了 原来你是在说谎
I see. So then, um, you were lying.
- 说什么谎？ - 说你的牌有多好
- About what?     - About how good your cards were.
那叫做唬人
Heh. I was bluffing.
那"唬人"是什么？
Aha. And what is "bluffing"?
不就是说谎吗？
Is it not another word for lying?
好了 很抱歉要终止这场派对
Okay, sorry to break up this party...
但是我得在明天上班前把履历表发出去
...but I've got resumes to fax before work tomorrow.
- 哇哦…   - 瑞秋 我们得定局
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.     - Rach, we've got to settle.
定什么局？
Settle what?
为维吉尼亚州 詹姆士镇的殖民地下定局
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
那块地是乔治国王要给我们的…
You see, King George is giving us the land, so...
瑞秋 这场牌局 这局你欠我们钱
The game, Rachel. The game. You owe us money for the game.
对哦
Oh, right.
这样吧 这是她们第一次玩牌 我们就算了好不好？
You know what, guys? It's their first time. Why don't we forget about the money?
才不要 我们会付的
Hell, no. We'll pay.
好吧 摩妮卡 我已经准备好另一个答案
Okay, Monica, I had another answer all ready.
这样好了
And you know what?
- 我们再来一场   - 我没问题
- We want a rematch.     - Well, that's fine with me.
我有钱
Could use the money.
基本上 你们就是靠从朋友那边赢钱来过瘾的
So, basically, you get your ya-yas by taking money from all of your friends.
- 没错   - 对 我靠去宜家过瘾
- Yeah.     - Yes, and I get my ya-yas from lkea.
家具得自己组装 但是便宜一点
You have to put them together yourself, but they cost a little less.
瑞秋 我玩扑克牌的目的就是想赢 好吗？
Look, Rachel, this is poker. I play to win, all right?
我要赢 别人就得输
In order for me to win, other people have to lose.
你要跟我玩扑克牌 就别指望我当好好先生
So if you're gonna play poker with me, don't expect me to be a nice guy.
因为一发牌…
Okay, because once those cards are dealt...
怎样？
Yeah?
我就不是好好先生
I'm not a nice guy.
好了 大家来吃吧
All right, boys. Let's eat.
你在"我爱瑞秋"披萨店买的吗？
Ah, did you get that from the "I Love Rachel" pizzeria?
- 你还在想那个？ - 拜托
- You still on that?     - Come on.
那场"我是坏男人"演讲 是怎么回事？
What was with that whole Black Bart speech?
"我一玩扑克牌 就不是好好先生"
"When I play poker, I'm not a nice guy".
老兄 完全搞错了
You're way off, pal.
我可不这么认为 罗斯 我认为你爱她
No, I don't think so. See, Ross, because I think you love her.
没有
Uh, no.
我对她有过好感 那都过去了
See, I might have had feelings for her at one time. Not anymore.
我只是… 马塞尔
I just... Marcel.
你拿那片CD干什么？不可以再放了
Where are you going with that disk? You are not putting that on again.
马塞尔… 好 敢按下那个键 你就完蛋
Marcel... Okay. If you press that button, you are in very, very big trouble.
真不敢相信 罗斯居然那么浑蛋
You believe what a jerk Ross was being?
对啊 他还真是好胜
Yeah, I know. He can get really competitive.
干嘛啊？
What?
摩妮卡 你是五十步笑百步吧
Oh. "Hello, Kettle, this is Monica. You're black."
拜托
Please.
我没有像罗斯那么糟
I am not as bad as Ross.
抱歉 我看不出差别 记得比手画脚事件吗？
Oh, I beg to differ. The Pictionary incident?
那不是什么事件
That was not an incident.
我正在比手画脚 盘子就溜出去了
I was gesturing and the plate slipped out of my hand.
哦
Oh.
- 我有面试 我有面试了   - 真的吗？哪里？
- Oh! I got an interview. I got an interview.     - You're kidding. Where? Where?
- 萨克斯百货公司 第五大街   - 哇 瑞秋
- Saks Fifth Avenue.     - Oh, Rachel.
这就好像母船来召你回家乡了
Oh, it's like the mother ship is calling you home.
- 是什么样的职位？ - 助理采购人员
- Well, what's the job?     - Assistant buyer.
我可以靠血拼…
Oh! I would be shopping...
吃饭
...for a living.
好 爱瑞丝阿姨来了
Okay, look. That's Aunt Iris.
她5岁就开始玩扑克牌了
This woman has been playing poker since she was 5.
她说的每一个字都要注意听
You've gotta listen to every word she says.
- 你好   - 喜剧泰斗东尼•蓝道死了吗？
- Hi.     - Is Tony Randall dead?
- 怎么会？ - 我没听说
- Oh, why?     - I don't think so.
他可能已经死了 我好像刚刚开车撞到他
Well, he may be now because I think I hit him with my car.
- 我的天 真的吗？ - 假的 第一课 这就是唬人
- My God. Really?     - No, that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
告诉你们吧
Let me tell you something.
在扑克牌桌上听到的 通通不可以当真
Everything you hear at a poker game is pure crap.
- 好漂亮的耳环   - 谢…
- Nice earrings.     - Thank you.
各位小姐 坐下
Girls, sit down.
- 爱瑞丝阿姨 这是菲比 瑞秋…   - 好了 好了…
- Um, Aunt Iris, this is Phoebe, and Rachel...     - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我们开始吧 这里停车要计时收费
Listen, I am parked at a meter. Let's do it.
罗斯 拜托 我们能不能听点别的？
Ross, could we please, please, listen to anything else?
好啦
All right.
今晚我完蛋了
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
- 嗨   - 你好
- Hi.     - Hey.
你们猜 你们猜 你们猜
Guess what, guess what, guess what.
嗯 第五个牙医投降了 他们开始推荐薄荷口香糖了？
Uh, okay. The fifth dentist caved, and now they're all recommending Trident?
不是 是我的面试
No, the interview.
她好喜欢我 超级喜欢我
She loved me. She absolutely loved me.
我们谈了两个半小时 我们的衣着品味相同
We talked for, like, two and a half hours. We have the same taste in clothes.
我跟她表妹还去过同一个夏令营
Oh, I went to camp with her cousin.
这工作太完美了 我可以做得很好 一定可以
And, oh, the job is perfect. I can do this. I can do this well.
太好了
That's great.
而且她的故事超好笑的
God. And she told the funniest story.
好极了 你说出来 我们一定会笑的
Okay, great, you'll tell us and we'll laugh.
开始玩扑克牌吧
Let's play poker.
好 我们谈过了…
All right, listen, we talked about it...
如果你们不想玩 我们可以理解
...and if you don't want to play, we completely understand.
对 我们可以玩别的 像是 不知道…
Yes, yes. We can play some other game. Like, I don't know...
比手画脚？
...Pictionary?
很好笑 很好笑
Very funny. Very funny.
我们再给扑克牌一次机会吧 好吗 两位小姐？
I think we'd like to give poker another try. Shall we, ladies?
好啊 没问题
Yes, I think we should.
你要我洗牌吗？
Rach, do you want me to shuffle those?
不用了 没关系 我来试试看吧
No, no. That's okay. You know what? I'm gonna give it a go.
- 好   - 好
- All right.     - All right.
菲比欠7块5 摩妮卡 你欠10块
So Pheebs owes 7.50. Monica, you owe $10.
瑞秋 你欠15块
And, Rachel, you owe 15 big ones.
谢谢你教我们唱《斗鸡眼玛莉》
Thanks for teaching us "Crossed-eyed Mary."
那个我们一定要放出来的
You guys, we gotta play that other way.
7块5拿去 你们要知道 这钱被诅咒了
All right, here's my 7.50, but I think you should know that this money is cursed.
- 什么？ - 哦 诅咒是我下的
- What?     - Oh, I cursed it.
不管是谁花掉的 都会有倒霉的事发生
So now bad things will happen to he who spends it.
没关系 给我吧 反正我一直都很倒霉
That's all right, I'll take it. Bad things happen to me anyway.
这样我就可以用电影解除咒语
This way, I can break them up with a movie.
现在只剩下葛林扑克牌机 她欠我们15块
So that just leaves the big Green poker machine, who owes 15.
真是标准的…
Hmm, oh, it's so typical:
"我是个男人 我是带把的"
"Ooh, I'm a man. Ooh, I have a penis.
"我就是要赢钱 来显示出驾驭女性的权力"
Ooh, I have to win money to exert my power over women."
你们知道吗？我们还没玩完
You know what? This is not over.
我们会再来找你们 我们会赢 你们会输
We will play you again. And we will win and you will lose.
你们会求饶 我们会讥笑你们
And you will beg and we will laugh.
你们所有的钱都会被我们赢光
And we will take every last dime you have.
然后再一辈子痛恨你们自己
And you will hate yourselves forever.
你把我想讲的话都说光了 摩妮卡
Hmm. Kind of stepped on my point there, Mon.
钱你们要现在付吗？
So you gals wanna hand over your money now?
这样我们就可以直接跳过玩牌的仪式
That way, we don't have to go through the formality of actually playing.
没关系 我们来看看最后笑的人是谁 猴孩子
No, that's fine. We'll see who has the last laugh there, monkey boy.
聊天聊完了没有？要不要认真打牌啊？
Okay, are we done with the chitchat? Are we ready to play serious poker?
大家快看 单眼杰克的眼睛一直跟着我
Hey, you guys, look. The one-eyed jack follows me wherever I go.
好 好好打一场扑克牌
Right, okay. Serious poker.
不好意思 你要去哪里？
Excuse me. Where are you going?
上厕所
Uh, to the bathroom.
你是来上厕所 还是来玩扑克牌的？
Do you wanna go to the bathroom or do you wanna play poker?
我想上厕所
I wanna go to the bathroom.
- 好 我打电话叫披萨外卖   - 不行 不行 不行
- All right, well, I'm gonna order a pizza.     - Oh, no, no, no.
我在等那工作的面试结果
I'm waiting to hear from that job.
百货公司9点关 你那时候再吃吧
And the store closes at 9, so you can eat then.
没关系 我吃薄荷糖先垫肚子
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac to hold me over.
好 辛辛那提玩法 不下盲注 大家先下注
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds. Everybody ante.
好
Yes.
不好
Or no.
好
All right.
你的钱就是我的 葛林
Your money's mine, Green.
你的拉链开着 盖勒
Your fly's open, Geller.
你们知道我刚想到什么吗？
You guys, you know what I just realized?
杰克跟扑克只差一个字
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J."
很巧吧？
Coincidence?
所以我们也可以叫这"杰"克牌
Hey, that's "jo-incidence" with a "C."
- 菲比 菲比   - 我不跟了
- Uh, Phoebe. Phoebe...     - Yeah, I'm out.
我跟
I'm in.
我也跟
Me too.
我也跟 好 你是什么牌？
Me too. All right. What do you got?
你最好离莲蓬头远一点 因为我要出同花牌了
Well, you better hop out of the shower, because I got a flush.
呵 呵 呵
Well, well, well.
小子 别想逃 我有4张6
Hop back in, bucko, because I got four sixes.
我有4张6 我赢了 我真的赢了
I got four sixes. I won. I actually won.
天啊 你们知道吗？我要把小罗斯叠成一堆
Oh, my God. You know what? I think I'm gonna make a little Ross pile.
这是罗斯的 这也是罗斯的
I think that one was Ross'. And I think, oh, that one was Ross'.
你的钱是我的了 你一辈子都看不到了
Well, I have got your money. And you'll never see it.
你裤子的拉链还是开着
And your fly's still open.
你相信了
I made you look.
- 我跟   - 怎么可能不跟
- I'm in.     - I couldn't be inner.
摩妮卡？摩妮卡 你跟不跟？
Monica? Monica, in or out?
我讨厌扑克牌
I hate this game.
好 乔伊 换你下注了
Okay, Joey, your bet.
我不来了 就像一个廉价妓女…
I fold, like a cheap hooker who got hit in the stomach...
被一个脸上流脓的胖子揍到肚子一样
...by a fat guy with sores on his face.
不跟了
Oh, I'm out.
- 罗斯？ - 当然跟
- Ross?     - Oh, I'm very in.
- 钱德呢？ - 怎么可能跟？
- Chandler?     - Couldn't be more out.
我也不跟 喘秋呢？
Me too. Rachel?
我不但跟 而且还加注
Um, I will see you and I'll raise you.
如何？想再浪费钱吗？
What do you say? You wanna waste another buck?
不了 这次不会
No, not this time.
- 你的是什么牌？ - 不告诉你
- So, what did you have?     - I'm not telling.
- 别这样 给我看看   - 不要
- Come on, show them to me.     - No.
- 给我看看 亮牌吧   - 手拿开 不要
- Show them to me. Let me see.     - Get your hands out of there.
我有过这样的约会经验
You know, I've had dates like this.
老天 你就是输不起 对不对？
Boy, you really can't stand to lose, can you?
你整个脸都涨红了
Your whole face is getting red.
太阳穴的青筋也爆出来了
Little veins popping out of your temple.
而且上衣跟裤子也不搭
Plus that shirt doesn't really match those pants.
首先 我没有输
First of all, I'm not losing.
- 发牌吧   - 喂？我就是瑞秋•葛林
- Just deal.     - Hello? Rachel Green.
请稍等一下
Excuse me.
这是有关工作的
It's about the job.
芭芭拉吗？你好
Barbara, hi. How are you?
唔？
Uh-huh?
我了解
No, I understand.
喔 没关系 我很好 别傻了
Yeah, oh, come on. No, I'm fine. Don't be silly.
如果还有什么空缺 请…
Yeah. Oh, but you know, if anything else opens up, please...
喂？
Hello?
嗯
Hmm.
我很遗憾 瑞秋
Sorry, Rach.
对啊 一定会有别的机会出现
Yeah, you know, there's gonna be lots of other stuff.
是啊
Yeah. Okay.
我们玩到哪儿了？好
Where were we? Oh. Okay.
五张牌 11点或更高的
Five card draw. Uh, jacks are better.
没有万能牌 大家下注吧
Nothing wild, everybody ante.
瑞秋 我们不用再玩下去了
Look, Rach, we don't have to do this.
当然要继续玩
Yes, we do.
- 好 下注   - 下注
- All right. Check.     - Check.
我下5角钱
I'm in for 50 cents.
- 我跟   - 我跟
- Call.     - I'm in.
我跟你5角钱
I see your 50 cents...
然后加注…
...and I raise you...
5块钱
...$5.
我以为我们有5角钱上限
I thought, uh, it was a 50-cent limit.
我刚刚失去一份工作 我想加注5块钱
Well, I just lost a job, and I'd like to raise the bet 5 bucks.
有人有问题吗？
Does anybody have a problem with that?
- 完全没有   - 没有 没有
- Not at all.     - No, no.
输家呢？
Loser?
不了 我退出
No, I fold.
什么叫你退出？少来 这是干嘛？
What do you mean, you fold? Hey, come on, what is this?
我还以为 "一发牌 我就不是好好先生"
I thought that, "Once the cards are dealt, I'm not a nice guy."
怎么？你只会说大话而已吗？
I mean, what? Were you just full of it?
我跟
I'm in.
- 你要几张？ - 1张
- How many you want?     - One.
庄家两张
Dealer takes two.
- 你下多少？ - 我下2块钱
- What do you bet?     - I bet $2.
好
Okay.
我跟你的2块钱
See your 2...
然后加注…
...and I raise you...
- 20   - 哇
- ...20.     - Wow.
我跟你的20块钱…
I see your 20...
然后加注25块
...raise you 25.
我跟你的25块钱…
See your 25...
摩妮卡 把我的皮包拿来
...and, uh, Monica, get my purse.
瑞秋 里面没钱了
Rachel, there's nothing in it.
好 那就把你的拿来
Okay, then get me your purse.
好 拿去吧 祝你好运
Okay. Here you go. Good luck.
谢谢
Thank you.
我跟你的25块钱 然后加注…
I saw your 25 and I raise you...
7块钱
...7.
Teen.
乔伊 我囊中羞涩了
Joey, I'm a little shy.
没关系 罗斯 想问什么尽管问
That's okay, Ross. You can ask me.
- 你需要多少？需要多少？ - 15块
- What do you need? What do you need?     - Fifteen.
- 好 这里有10块   - 我有5块 5块钱
- All right, here's 10.     - Here, I got 5, I got 5.
- 谢谢   - 祝你好运
- Thank you.     - Good luck.
好 追加17块
Okay, I am calling your 17.
亮牌吧
What do you got?
葫芦
Full house.
你赢了
You got me.
噢
Oh!
- 没关系 那很难赢   - 我以为我们赢定了
- That's a tough hand to beat.     - I thought we had them.
没有好牌就是没有好牌 能怎么办？
Well, when you don't have the cards, you don't have the cards, you know?
但是你们看她有多高兴
But look how happy she is.
- 航空信   - 飞机？机场
- Airmail.     - Airplane. Airport.
《75空难》《航爆死亡角》《惊爆九重天》
Airport '75. Airport '77. Airport '79.
时间到
Time's up.
《枭巢扫荡战》
Bye Bye Birdie.
那是鸟吗？
That's a bird?
那是鸟
That's a bird.
好 换我了
Okay, okay, it's my turn.
开始
Go.
豆子？
Uh, Bean. Bean.
- 《布拉格的春天》   - 答对了
- The Unbearable Lightness of Being.     - Yes!
这你都懂？
That you get?